http://www.catholictv.org/privacy-policy

Jump to navigation
ALERT: December CatholicTV Magazine
You are hereHome › Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy: Boston Catholic Television Center Inc. a.k.a The CatholicTV Network, iCatholic (Media), Your Catholic Broadband Network, CatholicTV
1. Protecting your privacy
Your information is in no way shared with third parties for marketing purposes. (i.e., no tracking devices) Your account information is password-protected. CatholicTV does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 13. If CatholicTV learns that a posting is by a person under the age of 13, CatholicTV will remove that post. CatholicTV, or people who post on CatholicTV, may provide links to third-party websites. We are not responsible for, nor can in any way control, the privacy policies of those third party websites, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of every website visited.
2. Data we collect
Your name, address, phone number and email address is requested for purposes such as, but not limited to, providing subscription services, registering complaints, commendations or feedback on programming, soliciting for advertising by CatholicTV, updates for new events, etc. CatholicTV does not store credit card information. Credit card transactions are transmitted to a financial gateway, and we endeavor to protect the security of your payment information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. We may collect personal information if you provide comments or if you contact us directly. Please do not post any personal information on CatholicTV's forums (e.g., www.iCatholic.com) or pages that you do not intend to make public. Our web logs collect standard web log entries for each page served, including your IP address, page URL, device and browser used, and timestamp. Web logs help us to diagnose problems with our server, to administer the CatholicTV site, and to otherwise provide our service to you.
3. Data we store
Our web logs and other records are stored indefinitely. Although the information is stored in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security.
4. Archiving and display of CatholicTV postings by search engines and other sites
Search engines and other sites not affiliated with CatholicTV – including, but not limited to archive.org, google.com, and groups.yahoo.com – will archive or otherwise make available CatholicTV postings.
5. Interaction With Children Online
CatholicTV is committed to the protection of children’s online privacy. The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) governs information gathered online from or about children under the age of 13. Verifiable consent from a child’s parent or guardian is required before collecting, using, or disclosing personal information from a child under age 13. If a CatholicTV website intends to collect information about children under 13 years old, COPPA-required information and instructions will be provided by the specific web page that collects information about the child. The web page will specify exactly what the information will be used for, who will see it, and how long it will be kept.
6. Circumstances in which CatholicTV may release information
CatholicTV may disclose user information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to follow the legal process or in response to requests from law enforcement.
7. International Users
Due to the international dimension of CatholicTV, the data provided by the user may be utilized for the purposes identified in this policy, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. Such data may be stored on servers located in the United States. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data.
8. Feedback
We appreciate your feedback! Please let us know if you have any questions or concerns.
Support CatholicTV
Your gift helps CatholicTV deliver the Good News into millions of homes across the nation. We need your support to continue connecting people with Christ and the Church.
donate now
Connect
Email
Facebook
Twitter
YouTube
Instagram
Blog
CTV Magazine
Watch THE Mass
Ways to Watch
more ways to watch
readsubscribe
Get CatholicTV
Find CatholicTV in your area. Just enter your zip code and let your provider know that you want CatholicTV in your home.
Get It!
Let Us Pray
CatholicTV is a powerful community of prayer. Send us your intentions; we will all pray for you!
Send My Prayer
iCatholic
Join CatholicTV’s online community and share your Faith with so many others in so many ways. We are the living Church online.
Join Now!
Find an Episode
1. choose the show
- Search All Shows -A Journey through Amoris LaetitiaA Word With WeberAdvent | ChristmasAdventures of a New EvangelistAdventures of Ryan Defrates: Secret AgentAging GracefullyAmerica's Catholic Television NetworkBlinkBreaking Bread Bruce Downes: The Catholic GuyCambio de agujasCatholic CoursesCatholic DestinationsCatholic FocusCatholic NewsbreakCatholic UndergroundCatholics Come HomeCatholicTV MassCatholicTV PresentsChaplet of Divine MercyChildren’s Liturgy of the Word Consecrated LifeContext with Lorna DueckConversation with Cardinal DolanCristo Para TodosDaily Living with Father ChapinDios Nunca DuermeDivine OfficeDr. Wonder's WorkshopEncounterEvangelista Bible StudyEverything You Wanted to Know About Catholic LiturgyFamily TheaterFatima GemsFlorida CatholicTVFocus on the Immaculate HeartGifts of the ChurchGoing My WayGrace of YesHouse+HomeInter NosIrish CatholicTVJust Live It!Knights of ColumbusKNXT RosaryLa Santa MisaLent - Holy WeekLenten Journey with Cardinal SeánLifelinesLive With PassionLord, Teach Us To PrayMaryknoll Lay MissionersMercy in the CityMessiahMomnipotentMysteries of The ChurchNational Shrine MassNo Greater LoveNotre Dame MassOn a Sacred NoteOur Common HomeOur Daily BreadOur Faith in ActionPapal ProgrammingPerpetual Help NovenaPersonally CatholicPope Francis | Daily MassPrayer and FastingReal to ReelRENEWEDRepent and SubmitRestored: Stories of EncounterSaints & SeasonsSilent SaintsSisterhoodStations of the CrossStumbleSunday to SundayTelethonTen Things To Know About JesusTen Things We Want You To Know About The Catholic FaithTestimoniesThe Catholic Talk ShowThe CatholicTV NetworkThe Choices We FaceThe Church AliveThe Faithful TravelerThe Fred and Susie ShowThe GistThe Joy of MusicThe LensThe Rebuilt ShowThe RosaryThe Rosary with Father FrankThe Way of BeautyThe Word ExposedThis Is The DayToo Blessed to be StressedViaggio a RomaWe've Got To TalkWhere God WeepsWords and ActionsWords of Francis - Bishop of RomeWOW: The CatholicTV Challenge
2. search episode descriptions and titles
3. Optional
Date
E.g., 2020-12-11
Join Us
Be part of the CatholicTV family of viewers. Stay in tune with what’s on and what’s coming up on your favorite Catholic television station!
Join The Family
